(Amy:)Kiss me
where I've never been kissed before.
You mean like SaIt Lake City?
(Amy:)Never mind. I'll talk to Penny.
(Howard:)Thank you.
(Amy:)Will you listen to me
play my harp now?
(Sheldon:)No. I dislike the sound of the harp.
(Sheldon:)Its overuse
in classic television sitcoms...
(Sheldon:)...always makes me think I'm going
to experience an episode from my past.
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry, Mommy. Don't be mad at me.
Don't do that.
(Leonard:)I don't know about this, Howard.
(Howard:)What? You're having trouble
with the long-distance love-making.
(Howard:)This is your answer.
(Howard:)There are two interfaces
that simulate a human mouth.
(Howard:)You have one, Priya has one in India.
When you move your Iips and tongue...
(Howard:)...it transmits exactly
what you're doing to hers.